{
	"questions":
	[
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Knight",
			"answer": "Marghek"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Knights",
			"answer": "Marghogyon"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Knight",
			"answer": "An marghek"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Knights",
			"answer": "An marghogyon"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Author (male)",
			"answer": "Awtour"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Authors (male)",
			"answer": "Awtours"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Author (male)",
			"answer": "An Awtour"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Authors (male)",
			"answer": "An Awtours"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Author (female)",
			"answer": "Awtoures"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Authors (female)",
			"answer": "Awtouresow"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Author (female)",
			"answer": "An Awtoures"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Authors (female)",
			"answer": "An Awtouresow"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Teacher (male)",
			"answer": "Dyskador"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Teachers (male)",
			"answer": "Dyskadoryon"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Teacher (male)",
			"answer": "An Dyskador"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Teachers (male)",
			"answer": "An Dyskadoryon"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Teacher (female)",
			"answer": "Dyskadores"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Teachers (female)",
			"answer": "Dyskadoresow"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Teacher (female)",
			"answer": "An Dyskadores"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Teachers (female)",
			"answer": "An Dyskadoresow"
		}
	]
  }
  